holiday-velvet.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Holiday Velvet Help

Paged

Protecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to Holiday Velvet; therefore, we conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and data security. We hope the policy outlined below will help you understand what data Holiday Velvet may collect and how Holiday Velvet uses that data.

**Personal data**  
Through our website, Holiday Velvet will not collect any personal data about you (e.g. your name, telephone number or e-mail address), unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with it (e.g. by registration, booking), respectively, provide your consent, or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal data.

**Purpose of Use**  
When you do provide us with personal data, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific information or offers. For the purpose of completing your booking we will disclose your name and contact details to the relevant accommodation with which a booking is made. 

**Cookies**  
As you browse holiday-velvet.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with holiday-velvet.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. 

**We do not sell or otherwise market your personal data to third parties.**
